{"data":[{"question":"What was she said convinced me that I was mistaken.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"was","c":"few","d":"their","answer":"4","explain":"- Their-> his","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A well tool-box is a handy thing to have in the house.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"woman","b":"come","c":"know","d":"well","answer":"2","explain":"- Come-> comes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"One of his less attractive trait is criticizing his wife in public.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"live","b":"is","c":"on","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"- Is-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The driver was tooting his horn as he reached the bend.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"and","c":"box","d":"along","answer":"3","explain":"- Box-> boxes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Try to more positive in dealing with the problem.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"up","b":"that","c":"took","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"- Took-> take","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"She had real psyched herself up for the big match.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"for","c":"in","d":"older","answer":"1","explain":"- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The woman who come in does not know the man well.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Sometimes","b":"me","c":"hours","d":"finishing","answer":"4","explain":"- Finishing-> to finish","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I live in Elgol, is a small village on the south-west coast of the island.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"goodest","b":"teaching","c":"moral","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"- Goodest->best","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I stop for passengers and empty the five post box along the road.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the","b":"and","c":"of","d":"lives","answer":"3","explain":"- Of-> about","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I pick up the school children that live along my route and took them to the school in Broadford.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a","b":"retired","c":"oldest","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"- A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}